翻译   草草
翻译   somehacker
时间轴   吉吉
后期   饿得慌
顾问   老杜
鸣谢   忙成狗的网飞
鸣谢   阿小小海
特效   草草
校对   草草
总监   草草
纸牌屋
第三季  第十三集
证据增加  美军海豹突击队
参与约旦河谷行动
漂白水
丙酮
第一夫人未出席活动
业主下周要来
Owner's coming in next week.
如果有不入账的员工  他会唯我是问
Anybody off the books, he'll be on my ass.
如果我跟贝尼托换双轮班  可以吗
If I switch some doubles with Benito, is that okay?
你们自己解决吧
Whatever you and him wanna work out.
欢迎来到加拉加斯  现在是3点21分...
Welcome to Caracas. The time is 3:21--
我们已经撒谎很长时间了  弗兰西斯
We've been lying for a long time, Francis.
当然
Of course we have.
想想如果我们开始说出真相  选民会怎么想
Imagine what the voters would think if we started telling the truth.
不是对选民
Not to them.
是对彼此
To each other.
什么意思
What do you mean?
算了吧
You know what? Never mind.
不  我们怎么对彼此撒谎了
No. How have we been lying to each other?
-我们没有  -你刚刚才那么说
- We're not. - You just said that.
我们即将在得梅因降落
We've begun our final descent into Des Moines.
请坐好并系好安全带
Please find a seat and put your seat belts on.
我们要谈谈吗
Should we talk?
不  我不该说什么的
No. I shouldn't have said anything.
她在哪
Where is she?
告诉我她在哪
Tell me where she is.
我不知道
I don't know, man.
-你不知道  -我不知道
- You don't know? - I don't know.
天呐
God!
我不会再问第二遍了
I'm not asking again.
-我的电脑  -我看过了
- My computer. - I tried that.
-锁着呢  -我给你密码
- It's locked. - I'll give you the code.
-你没有别的了吗  -我就这些
- You don't have anything more? - That's all I have.
-这是多久之前  -她就在那里  我保证
- How current is this? - She's there, I promise.
我找到过你一次  我还能再找到你
I found you once. I can find you again.
如果信息有误  你死定了
If this information is wrong, you die.
你试图联系她  你死定了
You try to contact her, you die.
弗兰克·安德伍德是个危险的人
Frank Underwood is a dangerous man.
权力如果掌握在不诚实的人手里
Because power in the hands of those who lack honesty,
便会失去道德的指引
lacks a moral compass.
而失去了道德的指引  权力便会胡作非为
And without a moral compass, power runs amok.
希瑟·邓巴可以质疑我丈夫的选择
Heather Dunbar can question my husband's choices.
她可以批评他的政策
She can criticize his policies.
但中伤他的人品只能说明她已孤注一掷
But to cast aspersions on his character is proof of desperation.
他竟然能对美军战士的死因撒谎
If he will lie about the death of a US soldier,
那他还说了什么谎
what else is he lying about?
我们知道他已经就2016年不参选一事撒了谎
We know he already lied about not running in 2016.
爱荷华州的人民能分辨是非
The people of Iowa know better.
他们看到了我看到的人
They see the same man I see:
一个强势  果决的领导人  虽然不总迎合民意
a strong, decisive leader who doesn't always do what's popular,
但总做正确的选择
but he always does what's right.
你们下周二的决定
The decision you make next Tuesday
将伴随你们多年
is one you'll live with for years.
三十年来  我一直陪伴在丈夫身边
For three decades, I've stood by my husband's side.
因为我知道他为你们这样的人说话
Because I know he stands up for people like you.
你们有选择的权力
You have the power to choose.
选择进步  而非小气
Choose progress over pettiness.
权力在你们  不在他
You have the power, not him.
选一个总统  而非装相的
Choose a president over a charlatan.
女士们先生们  有请我丈夫
Ladies and gentlemen, my husband,
弗兰克·安德伍德总统
President Frank Underwood.
谢谢  谢谢大家
Thank you! Thank you very much.
我告诉你们希瑟·邓巴
I'm gonna give you one good reason
周二为什么毫无胜算
why Heather Dunbar doesn't stand a chance on Tuesday.
她身边没有克莱尔·安德伍德
She doesn't have Claire Underwood standing by her side.
我想花点时间  谈谈我们将
I want to spend a few minutes talking about the future
共同创造的未来
that we are going to build together.
我说共同  因为我一个人做不来
And I say together, because I can't do it alone.
我需要你们帮忙
I need your help.
去后面见我
Meet me out back.
-拿了吗  -嗯  你呢
- You have it? - Yeah. How about you?
凯茜·洛克哈特
Cassie Lockhart.
社保卡  驾照  出生证明
Social Security card, driver's license, birth certificate.
没问题的
It's all legit.
为什么叫"凯茜"  都不是正式的名字
Why "Cassie"? It's not even a real first name.
那只是类似"凯珊德拉"这种名字的昵称
I mean, if it were short for something, like Cassandra.
-但作为正式名字  -不差你的
- But as your legal name? - It's all there.
凯茜  给你个挣回一百的机会
Hey, Cassie, take a hundred back if you want it.
我的卡车就在那边
My truck's right there.
留着吧
You keep it.
走吧  我都给你打折了  感谢我一下嘛
Come on. I gave you a big discount. Show some gratitude.
回去找你老婆孩子吧
Go home to your wife... and kids.
我要你操我  弗兰西斯
I want you to fuck me, Francis.
-我工作呢  -闭嘴
- I'm working. - Shut up.
你怎么了
What is going on?
我要你狠狠地操我
I want you to be rough with me.
-来啊  -克莱尔
- Take me. - Claire.
-听着  -来啊  快点
- Now, listen. - Do it. Now!
你想要什么
Is this what you want?
-你要这样吗  -对
- You want this? - Yes.
-没错  -要我来狠的
- Yes. - You want it rough?
我要你看着我
I want you to look at me.
你看着我做
Look at me while you do it.
我猜到了
That's what I thought.
请为第一夫人安排一间房间
Yes, I'd like to arrange a room for the First Lady, please.
是的  马上
Yes, right away.
你早上还是回华盛顿吧
I think you should go back to Washington in the morning.
抱歉来迟了  昨晚在商店值了双轮班
Sorry I'm late. I did a double at the store last night.
-没事  -我快点干
- No worries. - I'll work quick.
大概20万英里里程
About 200,000 miles.
是不咋地  但跑起来没问题
It's not much to look at, but... it runs well.
-多少钱  -一千二
- How much? - Twelve hundred.
但这车没手续
But I don't got a title, so
所以你就算当零部件买了
technically, you're just buying it for parts.
油箱满的吗
Have gas in the tank?
嗯  你可以直接开走
Yeah, you can drive her right out.
-但你需要车牌  -嗯  我有
- You'll need plates, though. - I got plates.
-现金可以吗  -我们只要现金
- Cash okay? - It's all we take.
安德伍德  安德伍德  安德伍德
Underwood! Underwood! Underwood!
嗯  没问题
Yes, I'm good.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
有请美国总统  弗兰克·安德伍德
the President of the United States, Frank Underwood!
谢谢  谢谢大家
Thank you! Thank you very much.
能回到爱荷华城太好了
It's good to be back in Iowa City!
克莱尔今天不能到场  但她要我转达
Claire couldn't be here today, but she wants you to know
她可是鹰眼队的大球迷
she's a big Hawkeyes fan.
在全国最优秀的公立大学之一
Now here, at one of the country's finest public universities,
我想跟大家谈谈希瑟·邓巴  对...
I wanna talk to you about Heather Dunbar's preference for--
-你明天能再值双轮班吗  -可以
- Hey, can you do another double tomorrow? - Yeah, no problem.
-好  那晚安  -你也是
- All right, have a good night. - You, too.
你好  我是凯茜·洛克哈特
Hi, I'm Cassie Lockhart.
你好  我是凯茜
Hello. Cassie.
凯茜  CASSIE
Cassie. C-A-double-S-I-E.
洛克哈特  LOCKHART
Lockhart. L-O-C-K-H-A-R-T.
4月21日出生  稍等
April 21st-- Just a second! -
我给你房租
I've got rent money for you--
不不  我有好消息
No, no, no, no. I have good news.
比安卡拿到保护身份了
Bianca got her protected status.
天呐  太棒了
Oh, my God! That's so great!
她感谢你帮她做手续工作
She says thank you for all your help with her paperwork.
-不客气  -我们要庆祝一下
- Of course. - We're celebrating.
玛莉娅从她周四干活儿的家里拿了酒来
Maria got a bottle from her Thursday house.
他们给我庆祝节日的
They gave it to me for the holidays.
不错啊
This is nice.
是啊  太糟了
I know, it's really terrible.
她在休斯敦有家人
She has family in Houston.
会帮她上社区大学
They're gonna help her get into community college.
我真替她开心
I'm so happy for her.
你呢  你不会永远待在这里吧
What about you, eh? You're not staying here forever.
等我攒够钱  我想买辆车
Once I save up enough, I want to get my own car.
然后再攒钱买房
And have enough for my own place.
在桑塔吗
Here in Santa?
北边吧  在林子里什么地方
Up north, I think. In the woods somewhere.
我想念树和雨了
I miss the trees and the rain.
找个安静的地方
Someplace quiet.
换个环境
Something new.
嗯
Yeah.
你是个聪明的姑娘  丽萨
Well, you're a smart girl, Lisa.
你一定都会如愿的
I'm sure you're gonna get everything you want.
如果比安卡能做到  你就能
If Bianca can do it, you can.
敬比安卡  和她的新生活
To Bianca! And her new life.
-干杯  -干杯
- Salud! - Salud!
先生
Sir?
您觉得她明天能参加吗
Do you think she can join us tomorrow?
-媒体开始有疑问了  -如果我们赢了
- The press are starting to ask. - If we win,
而获胜演讲时她没陪伴您
it'll be strange if she isn't standing next to you
会很奇怪
for your victory speech.
如果是落选演讲就更怪了
Even stranger if you have to make a concession speech.
如果我要做落选演讲
If I have to make a concession speech,
第一夫人不在就不是我们最该担心的了
the absence of the First Lady will be the least of our problems.
我要去跑步  能安排安保吗
I'm going for a run. Can you arrange the detail, please?
夫人  如果您公开去跑步  可能会...
Ma'am, if you run in public, it might...
怎么
Might what?
抱歉  夫人  我这就去安排
I'm sorry, ma'am. I'll take care of it right away.
不  如果我不能去跑  就说啊
No, if it's a problem with me running, tell me.
这可能提醒人们您不在爱荷华州
It might highlight the fact that you're not in Iowa.
请放这里
Right there, please.
安静
Quiet.
救命  不要
Help! No!
你要我再把你弄昏吗
You want me to put you out again?
张嘴  张开嘴
Open your mouth. Open it.
我不出声
I won't make any noise.
你敢出一声  敢动一下
You make one sound, or you move an inch...
-什么  -我不会的
- What? - I won't.
我不会叫的
I won't scream or anything.
纳特利将球传到...
Nataly puts the ball on the 44 ya--
耶稣在敲门...
Jesus is knocking on--
爱荷华党团会议只有不到24小时了
Less than 24 hours to go before the Iowa caucuses,
共和党票数分散  无人领跑
the Republicans have a broad field with no clear front-runner.
而民主党这边
For the Democrats,
安德伍德总统的民调数字冲劲十足
President Underwood has gained momentum in the polls.
很多政治专家认为民调数字的提升
A rise that many political experts are attributing
是得益于克莱尔·安德伍德参加了....
to the recent appearance of Claire Underwood in the--
所有大型民调都表示难分上下
Every major poll has it as a dead heat,
两名候选人都在45个百分点左右
with both candidates hovering at 45 percent.
还有10%的可能去参加党团会议的人
That still leaves one in ten likely caucus-goers
直到明晚才会做出决定
who won't be making their decision until tomorrow evening.
安德伍德夫人  总统电话
Mrs. Underwood, the president is on the phone for you.
安德伍德总统爱荷华竞选宣传的最后一天
President Underwood spent the last full day of campaigning
穿过全州  完成了他所有99个城镇的巡回宣传
traversing the state, completing his tour of all 99 Iowa counties.
-喂  -听我说
- Hello? - Listen.
不管明晚结果如何  我希望你陪在我身边
No matter what happens tomorrow night, I want you by my side.
你愿意考虑吗
Are you open to that?
克莱尔
Claire?
我早上飞过去
I'll fly out in the morning.
不不  你下午来就行
No, no. You can come in the afternoon.
你不用参加什么活动  或见媒体
You don't have to do any events or press, just...
只要我发表演讲的时候陪着我就行
be there with me when I make my speech.
-我同意了  -谢谢
- I said yes. - Thank you.
不客气
Of course.
昨晚
Last night...
别说了  我们明天见
Let's not. I'll see you tomorrow.
-好  晚安  -晚安
- All right. Good night. - Good night.
很抱歉我那么对你
I'm sorry for what I did to you.
真希望我能收回
I wish I could take it back.
我叫你安静了
I told you to be quiet.
我以为我杀了你
I thought I killed you.
我在新闻上听说你没事  我如释重负
When I heard on the news you were alive, I felt so relieved.
-我很怀疑  -真的
- I doubt that. - I mean it.
我为你祈祷
I would pray for you.
或许听上去很奇怪  但是真的
Probably sounds strange, but it's true.
我感觉很愧疚  你不该遭受那样的对待
I would, because I felt so bad. You didn't deserve what I did.
这都不会改变什么
None of this is going to change anything.
我们去哪
Where are we going?
无所谓
Doesn't matter.
还要开一会儿吗  我要尿尿
Is it gonna be a while? 'Cause I have to pee.
就在后面尿吧
You can pee back there.
那多不好  臭死了
You don't want that. The smell.
要么尿  要么憋着
It's either that or you hold it.
-那会疼的  -那真糟
- It hurts. - Too bad.
好啊  那我真做了
All right then, I'm gonna do it.
安德伍德夫人
Mrs. Underwood.
来  请坐
Please, come sit.
多谢前来
Thank you for coming.
我很遗憾事情闹成这样  太不幸了
I'm sorry for how everything has worked out. It's unfortunate.
我想你一定很不好受
I'm sure it's been difficult for you,
毕竟你投入了那么多心血
with all of the effort you put in.
就这样吗
Is this how it works?
他毙掉书  你来安抚我
He nixes the book, you soften the blow?
不  汤姆  不是那样
No, Tom, it's not that.
弗兰西斯根本不知道我找你来了
Francis doesn't even know I asked you here.
你为什么找我来
Why did you ask me?
因为我想问
Because I was wondering if...
我们是不是可以开诚布公地谈谈
we could talk honestly to each other.
不知道你是否愿意
If you'd be open to that.
-谈什么  -新罕布什尔
- About what? - New Hampshire.
你那天是有意让我晕过去的吗
Did you let me pass out that day on purpose?
我献血的时候
When I was giving blood.
我是让你继续说  我不知道你会晕过去
I let you keep talking. I didn't know you'd pass out.
你没想到吗
And you didn't see it coming?
你当时有话想说
You had things you wanted to say.
我说了什么  我昏过去之前
And what did I say... before I blacked out?
除了你写的  还有别的吗
Was there anything else other than what you wrote?
你不记得了吗
You don't remember?
不全记得
Some. But not all of it.
我是为自己问  我想知道
I'm asking for me. Because I need to know.
厌恶
Hatred.
你厌恶你和弗兰克多么需要彼此
For how much you and Frank needed each other.
我说厌恶了吗
I used that word? Hate?
是啊
You did.
你跟弗兰西斯
And of all the moments...
和我共度的这段时间里
that you spent with Francis and myself, you...
你认为我们是平等的吗
You believe that we're equals?
我被解雇了  安德伍德夫人  我不再受雇了
I got fired, Mrs. Underwood. I'm not on the clock anymore.
我和弗兰西斯之间的事远比你写的多
There's a lot more to Francis and me than what you wrote.
或许吧  但我没来得及问
Maybe so, but I never got a chance to ask.
那问吧  随你问
Then ask. Whatever you want.
你为什么没在他身边  去爱荷华州
Why aren't you with him? In Iowa?
我明天就去
I'm heading there tomorrow.
瞧
You see?
我问个问题  你们都不回答
I ask a question, and neither of you answer them.
这很累人  一遍遍敲打伪装的墙
It's tiresome, constantly swinging a sledgehammer at the façade,
只为了能从裂缝里一窥真相
just to get a glimpse through the cracks.
告诉我你看到了什么
Tell me what you see.
一个迷茫的人
Somebody who's lost.
但也不好说
But I don't know.
或许这样也好
Maybe it's all for the best.
我宁可想象你可能的样子
I'd rather imagine who you might be
而不是看到你真实的样子
than who you actually are.
祝你好运  克莱尔
Good luck, Claire.
够了
That's enough.
-能让我冷静  -那就在脑子里唱
- It calms me. - Then sing it in your head.
你能原谅自己吗
You're gonna be able to live with yourself?
这有什么意义
What's the point?
我伤不了你
I can't hurt you.
没人能找到我  或知道我是谁
No one's ever gonna find me or know who I am.
我永远不会说什么
I'm never gonna say anything.
安静
Quiet.
如果你是要惩罚我  没必要
If it's about punishing me, you don't have to.
去年一年  我不得不做的事
This last year, some of the things I've had to do,
我不希望任何人遭遇
I wouldn't wish it on anyone.
我叫你安静
I said quiet.
昨晚的内部民调什么结果
What did the overnight internals say?
还是难说  只有不到半个百分点的差距
Still a toss-up. Less than half a point gap.
-她还是我领先  -不重要
- Her or me? - Doesn't matter.
误差还是4.5%呢
The margin of error is four-point-five.
过去几天  领跑人换了三四次了
The last few days, the lead's gone back and forth three times.
归根结底  看出席率
Bottom line is turnout.
-先生  -嗯  我就好
- Sir? - Yes, I'm almost ready.
我能单独跟您谈一下吗
May I speak to you for a moment privately?
-好  谢谢  -我就在外面
- Yes. Thank you. - I'll be right outside.
我刚得到消息  安德伍德夫人推迟了过来的班机
I just got word that Mrs. Underwood has postponed her flight here.
-什么  为什么  -不知道  先生
- What? Why? - I don't know, sir.
另外  斯威夫特特工  她安保的负责人
Also, Agent Swift, the head of her detail...
他说汤姆·耶茨昨晚去了总统府邸
he said Tom Yates came to the residence last night.
-告诉沃恩我马上就过去  -是  先生
- Tell Vaughn I'll be down in a few minutes. - Yes, sir.
这里是克莱尔  请留言
This is Claire. Please leave a message.
是我  你收到留言后能给我回电话吗
It's me. When you get this message, will you please call me?
听我说  如果你深吸一口气
Listen, if you breathe deeply,
你会马上昏过去
you're gonna pass out right away.
-求你  -不会疼的
- Please. - Then nothing's gonna hurt.
道格  求你  求你
Doug, please. Please.
救命啊
Help!
没人能听到  躺下  瑞秋
No one can hear you. Lie down, Rachel.
听着  瑞秋已经没了
Look, Rachel's gone!
这才是我现在的身份
That is who I am now.
我知道你也不想
Look, I know you don't want to do this.
你可以
You-- You could--
你昨晚在停车场就可以杀我
You could've done it in the parking lot last night,
但你没有  你留了我一命
but you didn't, you kept me alive!
我知道你不是这种人
I know this isn't who you are.
求你
Please.
求你  求你  放我走吧
Please. Please. Please, just let me go.
求你
Please.
道格
Doug.
道格  求你  求你  放我走吧
Doug, please. Please. Please just let me go.
-求你  道格  -该死
- Please! Doug! Please! - Fuck!
总统又打来了
The president is on the line for you again.
你告诉他我不舒服了
You told him I'm not feeling well?
是  夫人  他还是想跟您说话
Yes, ma'am. He'd still like to speak with you.
告诉他我睡了
Tell him I'm sleeping.
我睡了  告诉他
I'm sleeping. Please tell him.
好的  夫人
Yes, ma'am.
喝吧
Here.
你那晚为什么要逃
I don't know why you had to run that night.
我只想保证你的安全
All I ever tried to do was keep you safe.
我害怕了  没动脑子
I was afraid. I wasn't thinking.
真抱歉
I'm sorry.
我知道你是善良的
I know you have a good heart.
你是想劝我放你走
You're saying that because you want me to let you go.
看着我
Look at me.
看着我  道格
Look at me, Doug.
你不用杀瑞秋
You don't have to kill Rachel.
她已经死了
She's already dead.
她死在了那片林子里  就这样吧
She died in those woods, and it's better that way.
反正她过得也不好
She didn't have a very good life.
但是...你要是真动手
But... But if you do this,
杀的就不是瑞秋  而是凯茜
you're not killing Rachel, you're killing Cassie.
而...
And...
凯茜·洛克哈特只想找个僻静的地方住下
all Cassie Lockhart wants to be is someplace far away.
没人找得到她的地方
Someplace where nobody'll ever find her.
她喜欢看电影
She likes to go to the movie theater.
不管上映的是什么
It doesn't matter what's showing,
她就是...喜欢爆米花的味道
just... she likes the smell of the popcorn.
她还想养条狗
She wants a dog.
黑拉布拉多
A black lab.
加上一张超大号床
And a queen-size bed.
弄好多毛毯  可以钻进去  她要的不多
Lots of blankets to curl up in. She doesn't want much.
她只想消失
She just wants to be invisible.
看着我
Hey, look at me.
我叫凯茜·洛克哈特
My name is Cassie Lockhart.
脚伸过来
Give me your ankles.
手伸过来
Give me your hands.
过来
Come on.
站起来
Let's go.
喝的水
Some water.
那边二十英里有个镇子
There's a town 20 miles that way.
首先  我想祝贺安德伍德总统
First off, I'd like to congratulate President Underwood
今晚赢得了选举
for his victory here tonight.
竞争很激烈  他最终取胜了
It was a tight race and he came out on top.
不要  不要
No. No, no, no, no!
我们可不是输不起
Let's not be sore losers here.
因为我们根本没有输
Because the truth is, we haven't lost.
我们才刚上路呢
We are just getting started!
我要感谢过去几个月来
I want to thank all the staff and volunteers
辛勤工作的员工和志愿者
who worked so hard over the past several months.
我们该走了
We should get going.
我想再给克莱尔打次电话  看她肯不肯来
I want to try Claire one more time. See if she'll come out.
哪怕她马上动身  也要等三个小时
That's three hours from now, even if she left this minute.
人们可以等啊
But the crowd will wait.
黄金时段不好浪费
We don't want to squander primetime.
等到凌晨一点  就没人看演讲了
A speech at one in the morning, we lose major viewership.
我的孩子们  和我亲爱的丈夫...
My children and my dear husband...
好  走吧
Fine. Let's go.
她不在讲台上  你打算怎么讲
How do you want to handle the stage if she's not on it?
我不需要讲台
I won't need a stage.
感谢大家的到来
Thank you for coming out.
非常感谢  谢谢
Thank you very much. Thank you.
非常感谢  谢谢  谢谢
Thank you very much. Thank you. Thank you.
爱荷华发声了
Well, Iowa has spoken.
他们的声音太响亮了
And they have spoken so loud,
我都不需要用麦克风了
that I don't even need a microphone.
我想在得梅因
Listen, I wanted to come down here
我们的竞选总部里
to our campaign headquarters in Des Moines,
不是像那个谁一样  在高档酒店宴会厅里
not go to some fancy hotel ballroom like you know who,
对你们所有终日努力工作的人说
and say to all of you who worked day in and day out,
在这场遍及爱荷华每个角落的选举中
on our behalf for this campaign, in every corner of this state...
我们今晚的成就全靠你们
It's because of you that we brought it home tonight!
你们肯定都想知道克莱尔在哪
Now, I know you're all wondering where Claire is.
有的人也许知道  她最近稍有抱恙
Some of you may know she's been a little under the weather.
她来自德州
She's from Texas.
还不太适应爱荷华的冬天
She doesn't understand these Iowa winters you have.
但她正在恢复  我今晚就飞回华盛顿
But she's on the mend and I'm flying to Washington tonight,
明天我就可以和她一起
so that tomorrow she and I can get on a plane
飞往新罕布什尔州  再拿下那里
and fly to New Hampshire, where we are gonna win there, too!
克莱尔
Claire.
他们说你在这儿
They told me you were down here.
我就想找个地方思考思考
I just wanted to come somewhere to think.
希望你好好想过了
Well, I hope you have.
也打消了你之前的疑虑
And that whatever was clouding your mind is gone.
因为我刚才一个人发表了获胜演说
Because I just had to give a victory speech... alone.
不管怎么样
And one way or another,
明天你一定要跟我一起上飞机
I need you on that plane with me tomorrow.
在桌子里
No. The desk.
左手边的抽屉
Left-hand drawer.
你还留着这个
You still have this.
是啊
Yes.
不知道为什么  觉得不该扔
It felt wrong to throw it out, for some reason.
我之前说到撒谎的事  我是想说...
When I said we were lying, what I meant was...
这么多年来  我以为我们在一起走这条路
For all these years, I thought we were on this path together.
但却跟我想的不一样
But it's not what I thought it would be.
不是我努力让自己相信的那样
What I convinced myself it would be,
像托马斯写的那样
like what Thomas wrote.
-我们是平等的  -我们是啊
- We're two equal parts. - We are.
你真的相信吗
You really believe that?
我们一起奋斗到今天
We earned this together.
我踏进办公室的第一天
I said that to your face
就当面对你说过
the first day I walked in here as president.
是你的办公室  不是我的
It's your office. Not mine.
我做的每个重大决定
I have not made a single major decision
都问过你
without asking your opinion first.
问题就在这儿  决定权都在你手里
But see, that's it. You make the decisions.
我想要的东西  比如联合国的事
Anything that I want, like the UN...
真让我恶心  弗兰西斯
It made me ill, Francis. My stomach turned.
为什么  因为你得辞职吗
Why, because you had to resign?
是因为我还得向你求助
No, because I had to ask for your help in the first place.
凭我自己没法拿下提名
That I couldn't get the confirmation on my own.
你有需要  找我帮忙怎么了
And what is wrong with asking for my help when you need it?
是我需要别人帮忙
The fact that I need it.
我厌恶那种感觉  那不像我
I hate that feeling. It's not me.
我照着镜子都已经不认识自己了
I don't recognize myself when I look in the mirror.
我会做像在爱荷华酒店里那样的事
I do things... like I did in the hotel in Iowa.
都没法跟你好好谈
I can't even talk with you about it.
你不说话  却想让我像畜生一样对你
Instead you want me to slap you around like some animal.
抛开一切  我们两个就是那样的关系
That's what we are when we strip everything away.
-那我能理解  -你简直是疯了
- That I can understand! - It was deranged,
要我那么上你
begging me to take you like that.
而你连这都不肯满足我
And you couldn't even give that to me.
你要是需要那样对你展现阳刚之气的丈夫
If you wanted a husband who proved his manhood to you that way,
还不如跟你妈待在达拉斯
you should've stayed back in Dallas with your mother
嫁个舞会国王
and married the prom king.
至少我还能知道自己的位置
At least I would've known where I stood.
你不能两者兼得
No, you can't have it both ways.
你高兴了就想要平等的关系吗
You want an equal partner when it suits you?
你想要男人掌控你就能要吗
You want a man to take charge when it suits you?
那我怎么办  猜你每次都想要什么吗
And I'm supposed to what, just divine when you want which?
别这么自私了  你比这强得多
Stop being so selfish. You're better than that.
-我没自私  -就是
- I'm not being selfish. - You are.
我们正在进行选举  看看咱俩
We're in the middle of an election, and look at us.
是啊  看看咱俩  弗兰西斯
That's exactly it. Look at us, Francis.
我们以前互相支持
We used to make each other stronger.
至少我以为是  可那也是假的
At least I thought so, but that was a lie.
我们是在支持你一个人
We were making you stronger.
我现在软弱又渺小
And now I'm just weak and small,
我受不了这种感觉了
and I can't stand that feeling any longer.
好吧  你想要什么
All right. What do you want?
你还有别的选择吗
What is the goddamn alternative?
求你了  克莱尔  我真的不懂
Please, Claire, tell me, because I don't understand.
我只听到你说不满足
All I am hearing is, it's not enough.
进驻白宫不满足
That the White House is not enough.
做第一夫人也不满足
That being First Lady is not enough.
-不满足  -不是
- Not enough! - No.
是你不满足
It's you that's not enough.
如果因为你...我们失败了
When we lose... because of you...
就什么都没有了
there will be nothing.
没有计划  没有未来
No plan. No future.
我们都会成为过去
We will only be has-beens.
你想成就点什么吗
And you want to amount to something?
那我告诉你残酷的事实
Well, here is the brutal fucking truth.
你可以恨我  可以觉得恶心
And you can hate me, you can be disgusted,
你有什么感觉都可以
you can feel whatever it is you wanna feel
因为我根本不在乎
because frankly, I'm beyond caring.
但是没了我  你什么都不是
But without me, you are nothing.
你说得对  这办公室只有一把椅子
You're right. This office has one chair.
你从一开始就知道这个
And you have always known that from the very beginning.
如果现在你接受不了这个
And if you now can't stomach that,
那我还真是个蠢货  当初居然娶了你
well, then I'm a fool for having married you in the first place.
但我没时间做蠢货
But I don't have time to be a fool.
我得治理国家  赢得选举
I have to run this country and win a nomination.
我在做我的工作
I'm doing my job.
道格也在做他的工作
Doug is out there doing his job.
你也该做你的工作了
And it's time now for you to do yours.
你要我掌控你吗  可以啊
You want me to take charge? Fine. I will take charge.
明天你给我上飞机
You will get on that plane tomorrow.
跟我去新罕布什尔州
You will come to New Hampshire.
给我微笑  跟人握手  亲小孩子
You will smile and shake hands and kiss babies.
在讲台上站在我旁边
And you will stand with me on a stage.
给我做你的第一夫人
And you will be the First Lady!
你要是都做到了
And you do all that.
私下里你可以随便恶心
I don't give a damn if you vomit on your own time.
计划20分钟后出发  先生
You're scheduled to depart in 20 minutes, sir.
谢谢  看第一夫人准备好没
Thank you. Check in with the First Lady, make sure she's ready.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
怎么样
So?
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我准备好了  先生
I'm good to go, sir.
请进
Yes?
夫人  总统要我问您准备好没
Ma'am, the president wanted me to check and see if you're ready.
夫人
Ma'am?
弗兰西斯
Francis.
我不去新罕布什尔了
I'm not going to New Hampshire.
你要去  车里见
Yes, you are. I'll see you in the car.
我要离开你
I'm leaving you.
克莱尔
Claire.
由于美国总统初选各州投票时间不同
所以最先举行投票的爱荷华州  新罕布什尔  和南卡罗来纳三州
其选举结果对最终选举结果影响非常大
如果候选人在这三州的初选中失利
将被认为缺乏竞争力  在接下来其它州的选举中
无论是选民还是捐款的金主  都会迅速离TA而去
所以在总统选举的最初阶段
候选人几乎会把全部精力放在爱荷华州和新罕布什尔州的竞选上
2008年  前第一夫人希拉里宣布参选
马上便被看作是民主党中最具实力的候选人
在爱荷华州初选投票前  无论是希拉里自己  还是媒体
都认为她应该能够顺利获得选举的胜利
然而由于过于轻敌  希拉里最终竟败给了一个不知名的政坛新秀  奥巴马
在爱荷华州的意外失手  彻底打乱了希拉里的选举部署
而奥巴马则凭借着爱荷华州初选的胜利在媒体上占尽风头
并乘胜追击  最后问鼎白宫